estorebuilder.com 2016-02-23

# eStoreBuilder

* * *

  1. **Consent for Collection, Use and Disclosure**
    1. Your use of the eStoreBuilder.com site and/or your registration for eStoreBuilder.com products and services constitute your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the eStoreBuilder.com site. A customer may withdraw his or her consent for collection, use and disclosure at any time by sending an email to unsubscribe@slimming.com. Please note that, if you do, eStoreBuilder.com may suspend its provision of products and services to you.
  2. **Accountability**
    1. eStoreBuilder.com collects, at the time of your registration and your sign-on to its web site, certain personal information (information that personally identifies you) including but not limited to your name, email address, home or work address, telephone number, and information about your computer hardware and software (e.g., IP address, operating system, browser type, domain name, URL, access times, and referring web site addresses).
  3. **Purposes for collecting personal information**
    1. eStoreBuilder.com collects and uses personal information for the following Identified Purposes:
    2. 3(a). to understand customer needs regarding eStoreBuilder.com' services;
    3. 3(b). to develop and provide our web site and our products and services for our customers;
    4. 3(c). to fulfill your requests for products, services or information;
    5. 3(d). to communicate with customers and site visitors, when necessary, and to inform customers of upgrades, as well as of other products and services available from eStoreBuilder.com, its partners and third parties;
    6. 3(e). to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or government request;
    7. 3(f). to respond to a legitimate claim, or to address our reasonable belief, that you are violating the rights of any third party or any of the agreements or policies that govern your use of the eStoreBuilder.com site or any eStoreBuilder.com product or service;
    8. 3(g). to protect the services, products or rights of eStoreBuilder.com, including but not limited to the security or integrity of the eStoreBuilder.com site; and
    9. 3(h). to identify and resolve technical problems concerning eStoreBuilder.com' site, products and services.
    10. eStoreBuilder.com also uses personal information in an aggregate form (i.e., not individually attributable to you) for its business analysis, operational, marketing and other promotional purposes. If we hire other companies to provide some products or services on our behalf, then we will only provide those companies the personal information they need for the Identified Purposes, and we will limit their rights to use and further disclose your personal information as appropriate in the course of their work for us.
  4. **Limiting the collection of personal information**
    1. eStoreBuilder.com limits its collection of personal information to only that information which is necessary for the Identified Purposes. eStoreBuilder.com does not direct its site to, nor does it knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen.
  5. **Disclosure, processing and retention**
    1. eStoreBuilder.com does not sell, rent or disclose your personal information to anyone else, except:
    2. 5(a). to someone you have designated to act as your agent, for one or more of the Identified Purposes (listed in Section 2, above);
    3. 5(b). to eStoreBuilder.com' employees, independent contractors, subsidiaries, consultants, business associates, service providers, suppliers and agents, acting on eStoreBuilder.com's behalf for any of the Identified Purposes;
    4. 5(c). as necessary if eStoreBuilder.com has reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with eStoreBuilder.com' rights or property, other users of eStoreBuilder.com' web site, products or services, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities; and
    5. 5(d). to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law.
    6. In addition, as we continue to develop our business, we may sell or buy other businesses or entities, or we may merge with another company. In such transactions, personal information may be one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that eStoreBuilder.com or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets. Your information may be stored and processed in the U.K., or in any other country in which eStoreBuilder.com or its subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities. By using this web site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. After your account becomes inactive (that is, if you request to be removed from our database), eStoreBuilder.com will keep your personal information in its archives. Your information will then be used only as necessary for tax reasons or to prove eStoreBuilder.com' compliance with any applicable law.
  6. **Accuracy of personal information**
    1. eStoreBuilder.com will use reasonable efforts to keep customer personal information accurate for the Identified Purposes, and for minimizing the possibility of making inappropriate customer decisions based on such information. Customers are responsible for informing eStoreBuilder.com about changes to their personal information. You can do this by calling UK: 0115 933 8320 & US: +44 115 933 8320. eStoreBuilder.com will use new or updated personal information it receives from customers to update its own records.
  7. **Security**
    1. eStoreBuilder.com will use reasonable efforts to protect customers' personal information.
  8. **Access to personal information**
    1. eStoreBuilder.com will afford you a reasonable opportunity to review the personal information in your file, if you so request by writing to: eStoreBuilder.com, 11 Castle Quay, Castle Boulevard, Nottingham, NG7 1FW, United Kingdom.
  9. **General**
    1. If eStoreBuilder.com is not able to provide access to some aspect of a customer's personal information, it will provide reasons for denying access such as; that by doing so would likely reveal personal information about a third party, or that it is confidential commercial information or attorney-client privileged communications, or that the information relates to a breach of an agreement or a contravention of law, or that its disclosure could reasonably be expected to threaten the life or security of another individual.
    2. Customers have the right to request that inaccurate or incomplete information be amended as appropriate, by contacting eStoreBuilder.com as described above. eStoreBuilder.com will promptly correct such personal information.
